relayhealth.com 2019-04-19

# Privacy Notice - RelayHealth Effective Date: July 24, 2018

                                   Privacy Notice - RelayHealth
                                     Effective Date: July 24, 2018
At RelayHealth Pharmacy Solutions (“RelayHealth”), a business unit of McKesson Rx Technology
Solutions (“McKesson” or “we”), we value the trust that pharmacies and drug manufacturers
place in us to appropriately use and protect personal information. This Privacy Notice informs
users of the RelayHealth website (“website”) about the purposes for which RelayHealth may
collect, use and share personal information and how it is protected. We want you to be clear
how we're using personal information and the ways in which we protect this information. By using
this website, you accept the privacy practices presented in this Privacy Notice. We encourage
you to read this Privacy Notice in full to understand our privacy practices before using this
website or submitting any personal information.
Scope
This Privacy Notice applies only to the RelayHealth website (www.relayhealth.com). RelayHealth
affiliates and subsidiaries may have separate websites, subdomains, and applications through
other web, mobile, cloud or SaaS platforms which are not subject to this Privacy Notice.
Additionally, RelayHealth business partners, ad networks and other third parties may have their
own websites and services with separate privacy practices. We encourage you to read the
privacy notices of all websites you visit to understand their privacy practices and your options.
Personal Information We Collect
When you visit this website, we may collect personal information about you. Personal information
is any information accessed, collected, or used by RelayHealth that identifies an individual, or
can reasonably be used to identify an individual, whether directly or indirectly. The personal
information we may collect includes, but is not limited to:
     •   Unique identifiers and user behavioral information collected passively, such as your IP
         address, location, browser type, operating system and clickstream activity
Tracking Technologies We Use
We use various technologies to collect personal information about users to this website. These
technologies include the following:
     •   Web Server Logs

             o  As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store
                it in log files. This information may include IP addresses, browser type, operating
                system, and clickstream activity. We do not link this automatically collected data
                to other information we may collect about you.
     •   Cookies
             o  We may utilize cookies. Cookies uniquely identify your device associated with this
                website. You can control the use of cookies by adjusting your browser
                preferences at any time. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your
                ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.
     •   Geo-location
             o  We may collect information about your location based on your IP address or
                data from location tracking technologies, such as sensor data from your device
                that may provide information on nearby Wi-Fi access points and cell towers. You
                may opt-out of geo-location collection by changing the setting of your browser
                or device.
     •   Other Tracking Technologies
             o  We also use local storage such as HTML5 to collect and store content information
                and preferences. Third parties who we partner with to provide certain features on
                our site use local storage such as HTML5 to collect and store information. Various
                browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 local
                storage.
These technologies are used to measure how you interact with this website in order to improve
the user experience. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies from
companies such as Google Analytics on an individual as well as aggregated basis. To learn
more about Google’s privacy practices, click here. If you want to opt-out of your data being
used by Google Analytics, click here.
How We Respond to “Do Not Track” Signals
Some web browsers have a ''Do Not Track'' feature. This feature allows you to tell websites you
visit that you do not want to have your online activity tracked over time and across websites.
These features are not yet uniform across browsers and not broadly supported. This website is not
currently set up to respond to those signals.

How We Use the Personal Information Collected
We may use the personal information we collect for purposes such as:
     •  Reporting or data analytics services
How We Share Personal Information Collected
RelayHealth does not sell personal information about you to third parties.
RelayHealth may need to share information with companies, organizations or individuals outside
of RelayHealth if we have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of that
information is reasonably necessary to:
     •  Meet applicable laws, regulations, legal processes or enforceable governmental
        requests
     •  Enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations
     •  Detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues
     •  Protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of our users, RelayHealth, or the
        public as required or permitted by law
     •  Engage in a merger, acquisition, reorganization, or sale of all or a portion of RelayHealth
        assets.
Access, Correction and Removal of Personal Information
This website is purely informational, and the only personal information that we may collect
through the website is limited to information collected passively, such as your IP address, browser
type, operating system and clickstream behavior.
If you are a RelayHealth customer, some RelayHealth applications allow you to directly access,
correct, update or delete your personal information through your profile settings. If this option is
not available, contact your account representative or privacy@mckesson.com to request your
personal information to be accessed, corrected, updated or deleted.
Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (''HIPAA'')
As a key provider of services and technology to the healthcare industry, RelayHealth has
implemented programs to address the privacy and security requirements of HIPAA.
Children’s Privacy

This website is not intended for any user under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect
personal information from children under the age of 13. We request that children under the age
of 13 not submit any personal information through this website.
How We Protect Your Information
We use reasonable and appropriate physical, technical and administrative industry safeguards
to protect information from unauthorized access, use, loss, misuse or unauthorized alteration. We
will make reasonable efforts to protect personal information stored on the website's servers from
unauthorized access using commercially available computer security products (for example,
firewalls), as well as carefully developed security procedures and practices. Notwithstanding our
security safeguards, it is impossible to guarantee 100% security in all circumstances. If you have
any questions about security on this website, you can contact the Privacy Office at
privacy@mckesson.com or the address listed below.
Changes to this Privacy Notice
We may periodically update this Privacy Notice to describe new features, products or services
we offer and how it may affect our use of personal information about you and your controls.
Since we may change this Privacy Notice, we recommend that you check the current version
available from time to time. If we make changes to this notice, we will update the “Effective
Date” at the beginning of this notice.
Contact Information
If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Notice, our information handling practices,
or any other aspect of privacy and security of your personal information, please contact us at:
Privacy@McKesson.com.
You may also write to us at:
                                         McKesson Corporation
                          ATTN: Privacy Officer (Privacy Notice, RelayHealth)
                                   2 National Data Plaza NE, 3rd Floor
                                           Atlanta, GA 30329
